



# Ana Emanuela Cisne de Lima

**Date of birth:** 26/07/1996 | **Nationality:** Brazilian | **Gender:** Female |

Phone number: (+55) 88997290946 (Mobile) | Email address:

cisneemanuela@gmail.com

Address: Rua Pereira Valente, 271, 60160250, Fortaleza, Brazil (Home)

#### **ABOUT ME**

27 years old and passionate about solving problems with technology, with good of professional experience. Web and Mobile Developer, with experience in React, Vue, Design Partners, Clean Architecture, Agile Methodologies, Git/GitHub.

Having a gerat experience in the area of Web development, I have already developed several applications with such technologies, which can be seen both in the LinkedIn highlights section and on my Github, along with a little more about me:

- https://github.com/MANUCISNE

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

01/11/2023 - CURRENT Remote

#### FREELANCE FRONTEND DEVELOPER WORKANA

- Frontend Developer: Proficient in JavaScript, React.js and Vue.js, with a focus on crafting responsive user interfaces and collaborating within agile teams.
- Agile Methodologies: Actively contributing to agile development processes, participating in sprints, and enhancing team collaboration for efficient project delivery.
- Next.js and TypeScript Proficiency: Developing skills in Next.js and TypeScript, applying them to optimize web application performance and contribute to the creation of engaging user experiences.

01/09/2023 - CURRENT Fortaleza, Brazil

### **IUNIOR OPERATIONS ANALYST** STB DESENVOLVIMENTO TECNOLÓGICOS LTDA

- Experienced in evaluating the accuracy of camera algorithms for specific point identification.
- Proficient in developing scripts to create accuracy charts and automate the analysis of data generated by camera systems.

01/11/2022 - 01/08/2023 Fortaleza, Brazil

## FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER DD SOLUTIONS DESIGN E DESENVOLVIMENTO

- Frontend Developer: Proficient in JavaScript and React.js, with a focus on crafting responsive user interfaces and collaborating within agile teams.
- Agile Methodologies: Actively contributing to agile development processes, participating in sprints, and enhancing team collaboration for efficient project delivery.
- Next.js and TypeScript Proficiency: Developing skills in Next.js and TypeScript, applying them to optimize web application performance and contribute to the creation of engaging user experiences.

### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/07/2023 - CURRENT Remote, Brazil

TECHNOLOGY IN SYSTEMS ANALYSIS AND DEVELOPMENT Universidade Anhembi Morumbi

Website <a href="https://portal.anhembi.br/">https://portal.anhembi.br/</a>

#### **INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY - FRONTEND DEVELOPER** ADA tech

Website <a href="https://ada.tech/">https://ada.tech/</a>

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **PORTUGUESE** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	B2	B2	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

#### DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office package: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access | Remote working tools (Slack, Teams, Zoom, Meet, Discord) | JIRA: working with Projects and Issues | Social Media including Facebook, WhatsApp and Twitter | GIT version control, Linux Command | Online collaboration tools (Miro, Trello, Asana, Zoom, Teams etc.) | React, Next.js, React Native | Vue2, Vue3, Vuex | jest library

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

## Organization in the Home Office: Where to Start? - 2020

The Healthy Home Office Collection is a collection of texts prepared by people from different parts of Brazil with the aim of making this ebook an instrument in response to the COVID-19 pandemic. It is a work made by people for people. We thank the authors for voluntarily dedicating their time to writing, the volunteers who carried out the editing, correction and everything necessary for the work to become a reality. This work is an extension of the efforts made during Home Office Week prepared by Startup Donna Home Tech and Cocreation Lab. Special thanks to the United States Embassy in Brazil and the alumni association USBEA - United States-Brazil Exchange Alumni, which through the Fund quick response alumni for virtual projects made the publication of this ebook possible. We also thank Inova Contestado, an Innovation Center located in the city of Caçador-SC, for their support.

## **RECOMMENDATIONS**

Yerlon Magalhães Front-End Developer at Dell Lead | Manager at STB Desenvolvimento Tecnológicos Ltda

Emanuela proved to be a very hard-working and proactive professional, carrying out development tasks that were quite complex for her level of knowledge at the time. Managed to develop Front-End structures for the system in a timely manner, according to the prototype and business rules raised.

Furthermore, he helped with the maintenance of existing modules of the system, where he demonstrated quick learning capacity and an excellent ability to work as a team with other project collaborators.

He also has the ability to analyze problems and suggest improvements and solutions. Additionally, he is a charismatic and easy-going person, with excellent communication skills.

Email yerlon.magalhaes@ddsolutions.dev.br

#### **VOLUNTEERING**

01/05/2020 - 01/09/2020 Camerron

**Global Combat Covid-19 Support Centre Team for Cameroon** Global Support Centre Health Team Member at SODEIT, Online Volunteer at United Nation Volunteers

